reading task for building a McDonald's I was excited when I heard that our
community was to have its own McDonald's restaurant I thought about all those
young people who would not have to go to the next town to buy their favorite
burgers and chips McDonald's cares about healthy eating too and works with
It is also cheap.
They often provide salads as well as burgers and chips.
Of course it also means more work for our area that needs jobs badly.
So I think they will be concerned about providing parking for the cars in our main street.
Many of our young people will be only too happy to work for the company.
McDonald’s makes a promise to the people who work for them.
They say, "We value you, your growing skills and your help to the company."
I can see nothing
but good if this company comes to build its restaurant in our town.
We are a small community and we enjoy our local dishes.
I am not sure if McDonald’s food is as healthy as they say in their advertisements.
This is very worrying.
Too many young people are getting fat through eating too much fatty food.
McDonald’s is not giving young people a good idea of what a healthy diet should be.
Local Chinese food, on the other hand,
is full of fresh vegetables and fresh meat and fish.
Although it is freshly cooked,
it must be less healthy than our own locally grown
and cooked Chinese food.
I also worry about all those cars bringing people to buy food at McDonald’s.
First, there will be petrol fumes(气体),
which will make our clean air dirty.
Second, there is the problem of all those cars that try to park
and prevent other cars from moving quickly through our town.
I am sure many young people will be happy to work for McDonald’s
but will they be treated fairly?
In America, McDonald’s does not allow workers’ unions to operate in its restaurants
and these are people who speak up for the workers.
If, as they say, the workers are happy with them,
why should they fear some workers joining a union?
So when I consider the food, the cars and the jobs,
I think we should not allow McDonald’s to build their restaurant in our town.